<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>release on EMBA BEYOND</title><link>https://www.securefirmware.de/tags/release/</link><description>Recent content in release on EMBA BEYOND</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 13:37:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.securefirmware.de/tags/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EMBA version 1.1.0 is out now</title><link>https://www.securefirmware.de/posts/version_110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 13:37:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.securefirmware.de/posts/version_110/</guid><description>In August 2020 we released EMBA to the world. 21 months or 1600 commits later version 1.0.0 was available. 1856 commits later version 1.1.0 with a huge amount of improvements and new features was released.
Just to give you a feeling of how massive this update is Initial release had around 3400 lines of code Version 1.0.0 had around 12000 lines of code And now, Version 1.1.0 has more than 20000 lines of code New system-mode emulation environment We have replaced the old system-mode emulation modules completely with a new and improved environment.</description></item><item><title>EMBA Version 1.0.0 is out now</title><link>https://www.securefirmware.de/posts/version100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 09:45:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.securefirmware.de/posts/version100/</guid><description>In August 2020 we released EMBA to the world. 21 months or 1600 commits later version 1.0.0 is available.
We are very proud of this release and we want to highlight some details in the form of &amp;ldquo;How it started&amp;rdquo; vs. &amp;ldquo;How is it going&amp;rdquo;.
Included modules In August 2020 we started with 26 EMBA modules. Today EMBA has around 60 public modules.
Lines of Code In August 2020 EMBA was already quite big with ~3400 lines of code.</description></item><item><title>EMBA v0.9.0 - Munich Edt released</title><link>https://www.securefirmware.de/posts/munich-edt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 12:55:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.securefirmware.de/posts/munich-edt/</guid><description>After around 1 and a half year of continuous development (and 1500 commits) we have decided to create our first official EMBA release.
Welcome EMBA v0.9.0 - Munich Edt.
Let&amp;rsquo;s celebrate our initial release!
Keep on using EMBA and improve firmware security!</description></item></channel></rss>