<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blackhat on EMBA BEYOND</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/blackhat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blackhat on EMBA BEYOND</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 13:37:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/blackhat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EMBA version 1.1.0 is out now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/version_110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 13:37:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/version_110/</guid>
      <description>In August 2020 we released EMBA to the world. 21 months or 1600 commits later version 1.0.0 was available. 1856 commits later version 1.1.0 with a huge amount of improvements and new features was released.&#xA;Just to give you a feeling of how massive this update is Initial release had around 3400 lines of code Version 1.0.0 had around 12000 lines of code And now, Version 1.1.0 has more than 20000 lines of code New system-mode emulation environment We have replaced the old system-mode emulation modules completely with a new and improved environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBA goes to Vegas baby</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lasvegas_intro_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 09:04:51 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lasvegas_intro_2022/</guid>
      <description>It’s official, in August Pascal and myself will present the firmware security analyzer EMBA at Black Hat and DEF CON in Las Vegas. We are super excited and happy to have the possibility to show you the best firmware scanner on the best stage! As this is not enough, we are planning to release a huge update for EMBA &amp;hellip; stay tuned&#xA;You can find further details at the Black Hat USA Arsenal page and the DEF CON 30 forum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBA Version 1.0.0 is out now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/version100/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 09:45:39 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/version100/</guid>
      <description>In August 2020 we released EMBA to the world. 21 months or 1600 commits later version 1.0.0 is available.&#xA;We are very proud of this release and we want to highlight some details in the form of &amp;ldquo;How it started&amp;rdquo; vs. &amp;ldquo;How is it going&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;Included modules In August 2020 we started with 26 EMBA modules. Today EMBA has around 60 public modules.&#xA;Lines of Code In August 2020 EMBA was already quite big with ~3400 lines of code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join us at Black Hat Asia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/emba_black_hat_asia_arsenal_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 12:38:59 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/emba_black_hat_asia_arsenal_2022/</guid>
      <description>You can attend the Black Hat Business Hall for free - check it out and join our talk on firmware analysis with EMBA here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Asia with EMBA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/blackhat_asia_arsenal_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:07:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/blackhat_asia_arsenal_2022/</guid>
      <description>It’s official, in May Pascal and myself will present EMBA the firmware security scanner at Black Hat ASIA 2022. We are super excited and happy to have the possibility to show you the best firmware scanner on the best stage!&#xA;You can find further details at the Black Hat Asia Arsenal page.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
